boh.com 2017-02-11

# Bank of Hawaii - Other - Bank of Hawaii - Online Privacy Policy

## Protecting the privacy of your information on boh.com.

Thank you for visiting Bank of Hawaii Corporation’s website. We understand the importance of customer privacy and want you to know what information is collected online and how we use it.

#### Contact Information You Provide Us and How It’s Used

When you supply us with your postal or e-mail address or telephone number online, via boh.com or third party sites such as Facebook®, Twitter® and other social media sites, you may receive periodic mailings, e-mails or telephone contact from us with information on new products, services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings or contact, please call us or write us at the telephone number or address shown on your account statement. Please provide us with your exact name, street and e-mail address. You may also request to unsubscribe from future marketing e-mails only from the e-mail itself by clicking the “unsubscribe” link that is included in every marketing e-mail.

Even if you make this choice, we may still send you e-mail to deliver your statements (which may include marketing materials) or give you account-related notices or other information. 

#### E-mails 

For inquires sent to us by e-mail and/or responses we send to you via e-mail, we preserve your e-mail address, our response and the original content of your e-mail for a period of time so we can efficiently handle any follow-up questions you may have. We also do this for legal, regulatory and account servicing requirements. Regular Internet e-mail is not a secure form of communication. Any information sent via e-mail should be of a non-sensitive and non-confidential nature. Submitting information via one of our online contact forms is secure as we employ encryption. 

#### Online Tracking and Online Advertising

Bank of Hawaii Corporation uses cookies to store customer preference information on the use of our site and to facilitate access to restricted web pages during a single online session. A session cookie (or ‘session variable’) is used to authenticate your login information. This includes accessing our systems via a desktop PC, a laptop, tablets and mobile devices.

In addition, certain applications on mobile devices may transmit information to us when you request information from the application. For example, when searching for a nearby ATM, your mobile device may transmit your current location to provide ATMs near your current location.

While you are logged on viewing your account information or conducting online transactions with Bank of Hawaii Corporation, we recommend that you do not access other websites during your online session. Always exit from your online session with Bank of Hawaii Corporation before moving to or accessing other websites and prior to turning off your computer. Some browsers allow you to reject cookies. However, if you set your browser to reject cookies, you may find that you are unable to conduct your online transactions with Bank of Hawaii Corporation. If you choose to NOT accept cookies while accessing web pages on the Internet, we suggest that you enable acceptance of cookies when you are logged onto your online session with Bank of Hawaii Corporation. For detailed instructions on enabling and disabling cookies, refer to your web browser’s online HELP menu or user manual.

We also use cookies to evaluate our website and to track advertising campaigns from banner ads, opt-in e-mails and through third party advertising services. These cookies and tracking pixels (also known as web beacons, action tags, floodlight tags, or transparent GIF files) contain an ID number that allows us to track the pages you’ve visited within our website. We aggregate this data with data on the pages visited by other users to track overall visitor traffic patterns to help us improve the organization of our site and to understand, for example, the effectiveness of our advertising and marketing campaigns. These cookies also allow us to present ads to you on third party sites on Bank of Hawaii products you may be interested in. The tags are industry-standard technology and are anonymous. No personally identifiable information is stored on these cookies or web pixels. Any company we use may not use these cookies for their own purposes or share the information in accordance with the contracts they have signed.

Bank of Hawaii uses the service of web analytic firm Adobe Analytics to track and report on advertising and marketing on boh.com and from third party websites.

If you would like more information about Adobe Analytic’s information gathering practices, privacy policy and “opt out” procedures, please “[click here.](http://www.adobe.com/privacy/policy.html)”

#### Web Logs and Browser Level Information

Our web servers automatically collect limited information about your computer configuration and browsing activity when you visit our site. This information includes the browser software that you use, the operating system of your computer, the resolution of your computer monitor, the speed of your Internet connection, the website that referred you to our site and/or the search terms you entered into a search engine to reach our site, etc. We use this information to make our website as useful as we can for as many users as possible.

#### Social Media Sites

Bank of Hawaii Corporation maintains social media sites, including, but not limited to Facebook, Google+, Instagram, LinkedIn, Twitter and YouTube and may interact with registered users of these sites. Any content you post to these sites (including pictures, information or opinions) as well as information you make available on these sites (e.g. your profile) is subject to the applicable site’s terms of use and privacy notice. We recommend that you review this information carefully.

#### Surveys

The information you provide from surveys and promotions will be used for internal marketing and for developing information that you may find useful. Additionally, we may inform you if a particular account or service would benefit you based on the information submitted.

#### Contests

We may occasionally run contests on our site and ask visitors for contact information (such as e-mail address or telephone number). Participation in these contests is not mandatory. However, if you choose to participate, we may send you information about the contest and our company. If you have participated in a past contest but no longer wish to remain on our contact list, please call us or write us at the telephone number or address shown on your account statement. Please provide us with your exact name, street and e-mail address.

#### Updates

If you are a current e-Bankoh online banking customer, you can provide updated contact information through our website. If you are not an online banking customer, please visit a convenient branch.

#### Contacting the Website

If you have any questions regarding this Online Privacy Policy or the practices of our website, you can contact us.

#### Children’s Privacy

We do not use the website to knowingly solicit personal information from children under the age of thirteen (13) without parental consent. We request that such individuals not provide personal information through our site. For additional information regarding the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), please visit the Federal Trade Commission website.

To view and print PDF files, please download the free Adobe Acrobat Reader.
